Fund for Adult Education (FAE) Records
Fund for Adult Education (FAE) Records
- Audiorecordings
  - [Untitled Fund for Adult Education Tape #1], fae_055; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 6)
  - [Untitled Fund for Adult Education Tape #2], fae_098; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 10)
  - [Untitled Fund for Adult Education Tape #3], fae_099; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 10)
  - [Untitled Fund for Adult Education Tape #4], fae_100; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 10)
  - [Untitled Fund for Adult Education Tape #5], 12/08/1952; fae_101; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 10)
  - [Untitled Fund for Adult Education Tape #6], 12/08/1952; fae_102; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 10)
  - [Untitled Fund for Adult Education Tape #7], 12/08/1952; fae_103; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 10)
  - [Untitled Fund for Adult Education Tape #8], fae_104; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 10)
- Audio/film sets
  These presentations, also known as slide/films, consisted of a silent 35mm film and a phonodisc intended to be played as the film was viewed.
  - Committee for Economic Development Presents "America’s Secret Weapon", fae_119; Film: 35mm (Box 99)
  - Committee for Economic Development Presents "America’s Secret Weapon", fae_125; VinylDisc
  - Committee for Economic Development Presents "The Last Three Feet", fae_114; Film: 35mm (Box 99)
  - Committee for Economic Development Presents "The Last Three Feet", fae_122; VinylDisc
  - CED Slidefilm "Mobilizing Main Street" Part 1, fae_115; Film: 35mm (Box 99)
  - CED Slidefilm "Mobilizing Main Street" Part 2, fae_116; Film: 35mm (Box 99)
  - Committee For Economic Development Presents "Mobilizing Main Street" (Executive Secretary, Industry, Commerce, Agriculture) Parts 1 and 2, fae_123; VinylDisc
  - CED Slidefilm "Mobilizing Main Street" Part 3, fae_117; Film: 35mm (Box 99)
  - CED Slidefilm "Mobilizing Main Street" Part 4, fae_118; Film: 35mm (Box 99)
  - Committee for Economic Development Presents "Mobilizing Main Street" (Executive Secretary, Industry, Commerce, Agriculture) Parts 3 and 4, fae_124; VinylDisc
  - CED Slidefilm "Now Is The Time", fae_112; Film: 35mm (Box 99)
  - Committee for Economic Development Presents "Now Is The Time", fae_120; VinylDisc
  - Committee for Economic Development Presents "Target for Peace" and "The Grass Roots Approach", fae_113; Film: 35mm (Box 99)
  - Committee for Economic Development Presents "Target for Peace" and "The Grass Roots Approach", fae_121; VinylDisc